almarsguides.com 2018-05-09

# Almar's Guides Privacy Policy

**Almarsguides.com Privacy Policy**

           Almarsguides.com is owned and maintained by Almar's Guides INC. Protecting your privacy is important to us and this statement is intended to make you aware of our commitments to you as an important visitor to our website. This policy may change from time to time, so check back periodically.

           Your use of this website indicates your acceptance of this policy in it's entire form. Also, this privacy policy is subject to change at any time at our discretion. Your continued use of this website indicates your acceptance of these changes. We may collect personal information about your visit and your use of our website.

           The website may use cookies to track your internet activities and your preferences. Cookies allow website's operators and 3rd party advertisers to identify you as a returning visitor and serve advertisements that are relevant to your internet preferences.

           Logs of user activity may also be collected.

           Your use of links located on our website that link to other website's may be tracked and recorded for our use. This website includes and utilizes Google and their Adsense advertising system to serve ads to visitors on our website. 

**Google Privacy Policy**

1\. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to display ads on this website.  
2\. Google's use of DART cookies enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your site and other sites on the Internet.  
3\. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
